kic.org.uk 2011-11-01

# Privacy Policy | Kaplan International Colleges

Kaplan International Colleges is committed to maintaining the privacy of your personal information. This Data Protection Policy describes how we treat information received about you.

## Information We Collect

So that we can provide you with the information, programmes or products you have requested, we collect and store certain information about you, including your name, telephone number, email address, postal address, age, educational background, credit card number and other payment information. If you are enrolling as a student, we also may also collect other personal data, such as information regarding your health so that, if necessary, we can make appropriate accommodation for you, or your race or ethnicity, so that we can report aggregate student diversity statistics. This data is considered “sensitive data” and you consent to our collection, storage and use of such sensitive data for these purposes.

We also may collect from you emergency contact information, such as the telephone number or email address for a friend or family member. You represent to us that you have obtained consent from your emergency contacts to provide us their information for this purpose. 

## How We Use Information Collected

We use this information to process your requests, review and confirm your qualifications, provide you with our materials and programmes and to otherwise contract with you. We also may provide you with promotional materials about our products and services and provide your information to our affiliates and other carefully selected companies, some of whom may be outside the EU, who would like to send you promotional materials about their products and services.

## Your Ability to Choose

You can let us know that you do not wish to receive promotional material from us by contacting us by email at kicinfo@kaplan.com or by post at 52 Grosvenor Gardens, London SW1W 0AU. You also can let us know that you do not want us to share your information with our affiliates or other carefully selected companies for promotional purposes by contacting us at the same email or postal address.

## Disclosure to Third Parties

We may hire other companies to perform services on our behalf including, without limitation, facilitating some aspects of our website and services, managing our database, sending email and other mail to you, processing and collecting payments, providing us legal, financial and accounting advice and conducting required audits. These other companies may be supplied with or have access to your information solely for the purpose of providing these services to us or on our behalf. We also may disclose personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is necessary under the law (for example, when necessary to protect our or a third party's intellectual property or proprietary rights) or when we, at our sole discretion, believe it is appropriate, in connection with a sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, or when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires us to do so.

Your personal data is accessible by and provided to our partner university, for administration purposes, such as keeping track of your student records, accepting and recording your payments, providing you with certificates of completion and complying with any regulatory reporting requirements. We may also provide your data to companies or authorities from which you seek funding. If you have enrolled in our programmes through your sponsor or employer, we may share your data and course attendance and study results with your sponsor or employer. Such third parties are not subject to this Privacy Policy. Contact our partner universities/your employer or sponsor/any funding institutions/ companies directly for information about how they treat your personal data.

## Transfer to Other Countries

We may need to process and store your information in countries outside the EU (and not subject to EU Data Protection laws), including, without limitation, your home country, the country in which you plan to graduate or other countries where we have offices or service providers. By providing your information to us, you consent to transfer of your information to these other countries. 

## Access and Rectification

If you would like to review, change or delete any information that we have about you, you can do so by contacting us on:

Tel: +44 (0)20 7811 3050  
Fax: +44 (0)20 7881 0710  

Kaplan International Colleges  
Kensington Village, Avonmore Road  
London W14 8HQ   
United Kingdom 

##  Questions, Comments and Concerns

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our practices, you may contact us on:

Tel: +44 (0)20 7811 3050  
Fax: +44 (0)20 7881 0710  

Kaplan International Colleges  
Kensington Village, Avonmore Road  
London W14 8HQ   
United Kingdom 

## Modifications

We may change this Data Protection Policy from time to time.
